Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1946-2003 and undated, (122 boxes)
  - Ford (Box 29)
    - Galaxy: Teaser, Flexible Working Hours, Special Restaurant (U. K. ). 1998. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 29)
    - Galaxy: Virtual Reality Video (U. K. ). 1998. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 15:00 (Box 29)
    - Ka: Only for You First Rendezvous (Germany). 1996. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 3:29(2 copies) (Box 29)
    - Mondeo Britain edits. Undated. VHS. PAL. TRT: 2:01 (Box 29)
    - Mondeo European edits. Undated. VHS. PAL. TRT: 2:00 (Box 29)
    - Mondeo launch film, GT version. 1996. VHS. PAL. TRT: 15:00 (Box 29)
    - Mondeo Taube spot (Germany). Undated. VHS. TRT: 0:30 (Box 29)
    - The Plan infomercial, Get Ready 'Cause Here It Comes (Canada). 1994. VHS. TRT: 60:00(3 copies) (Box 29)
    - The Plan 30-Minute (Canada). 1995. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 29)
    - The Plan 30-Minute (Canada). 1995. Digital Betacam. TRT: 28:30 (Box 29)
    - Puma (France). 1997. CD-ROM. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 29)
    - Puma, McQueen. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 29)
    - Red Carpet Lease, Words of Wisdom. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 7:00 (Box 29)
    - Spots: Parlament; Kiosk; Bus; Wintercheck (Germany). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
    - Sable Test Drive. 1996. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 29)
    - Various Ford and Lincoln-Mercury spots: Detroit; Toronto; Brazil; U. K.; Germany. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 29)
    - Video Explicativo Ford/MIRA. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 29)
  - Fortune Magazine
    - Clockwatchers. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 29)
    - Clockwatchers; Kiosk. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
    - Coin toss. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 29)
    - Conference Room. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 29)
    - Editorial. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 29)
    - Fortune in Support of Direct Mail (Radio). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 29)
  - Fortune Magazine (Box 30)
    - How'd They Do It? 1985. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 30)
    - How'd They Do It? Rev. 3. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 30)
    - How'd They Do It? Rev. 4. 1987. 1" Video reel. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 30)
    - How Far Can You See?1989. Umatic. TRT: 12:00 (Box 30)
    - Making It Again. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 1:20 (Box 30)
    - More Making It. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 30)
    - Radar. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 30)
  - Four/Four. Video presentation: Lipton; Roy Roders; Seagram's; Autolite; Old Style; Kraft; Pan Am; Jamaica; Fruitslush; Drug Free America; Maxwell House; Puffs; Miller; Gillette. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 30)
  - Foxtel
    - Beyond the Boundaries (Australia). Undated. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 30)
    - Compile as of 5/8/96 (Australia). 1996. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 16:30 (Box 30)
  - Frank Ferrante. Sample Reel: Popeel, Gadgets on Parade; Tut Totes; Vista Marketing classic spot; ICS; Time Life Books, Vietnam; Hallmark Cards; USPS, Father/Son; Dr. Pepper; Kodak, First Day of School; Jamaican Tourist Board; Merrill Lynch, China Shop, Modern Bull, Face 900#; NYTEL, Ten Minute Talker, animated spot; N. Y. Times, Steinbrenner Bellboy Pager, George Weather Phone, Grandma Buy Your Own Phone; CIT, Wedding, I Love Our Home. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 30)
  - Free FM. Captain Pecker (Australia). 1999. VHS. TRT: 1:00(2 copies) (Box 30)
  - Friendship Cottage Cheese. Spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 30)
  - Frito-Lay
    - Alomar Promo. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 30)
    - La Volkera. Undated. VHS. TRT: 0:45 (Box 30)
  - Fritz Wrap. Quotes. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
  - Fuji. Millennium campaign with Mr. Bean (Germany). 1999. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 31)
  - Future. com. Meeting the Challenge. 1998. VHS. TRT: 4:10 (Box 31)
  - Gasaworks/Mattingly. Beaurepairs and competitive spots (New Zealand). 1997. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 20:00 (Box 31)
  - Geico
    - Tape 1: It's Only Fair. 1978. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 31)
    - Tape 2: Highway; Cop; Applause; Recording Studio; Fireside Chat. 1978. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 31)
    - Mix. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 31)
    - Radio spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 31)
  - General Cigar. Silver Creek. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
  - General Electric. Mastercard spot. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 31)
  - General Foods
    - Bird's Eye spot. 1987. 1" Video reel. TRT: 0:30 (Box 31)
    - Bird's Eye Fresh Creations: Champagne Wrap. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 31)
    - Bird's Eye Juice Dispenser: Goodbye Old Friend; Training Master. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:40 (Box 31)
    - Cool Rappers. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 31)
    - Home Chef. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 31)
    - International Coffee: Mmm--That's Good. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
  - General Foods (Box 32)
    - Jell-O Frozen Novelties--Jopp: Answering Machine; Famous Face; Right Hand Left Hand. Crystal Light: Earned It; Belinda. Kool-Aid: Who's That in My Freezer? 1988. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 32)
    - Ronzoni: Crying and Laughing. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 32)
    - Ronzoni: Taste the Difference; Most Fun with a Fork; Teach Pasta; Teach Italian Pasta; Teach Italian Frozen Entrees. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 10:00(2 copies) (Box 32)
    - Shortcuts: Great Ideas $9. 95; Great Ideas $14. 95. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 32)
    - Shortcuts: What's for Dinner. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 6:40 (Box 32)
    - WMF Brewer: Fastest, Freshest Cup in Town. 1987. VHS. TRT: 7:00 (Box 32)
    - WMF Brewer film. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 32)
  - General Motors
    - General Motors, General Motors Mastercard spots. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 32)
    - Image (corporate identity program). 1992. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 32)
  - Genus
    - Homebuyers. 1999. VHS. TRT: 15:00 (Box 32)
    - Sprinkler; Café Couple. 1999. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 32)
  - Geo Magazine
    - Circulation, magazine montage. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 32)
    - German version. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 32)
  - Gevalia
    - Brazil: Brevlada; Brazilien. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 4:00 (Box 32)
  - Gevalia (Box 33)
    - Coffee Bar; Ice Lake. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 33)
    - Gevalia Coffee House. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 33)
    - Gevalia Coffee Sweden: Construction Workers; Tennis Match. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 33)
    - Unexpected Visitor campaign: Athlete; Dive; The Wall; The Adventurer; Top Gun; Bungy Jump; Bathtub; Rollercoaster. 1990-1996. Umatic. TRT: 20:00(2 copies) (Box 33)
    - Website. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 33)
  - Gillette. Right Guard--Tammy Wrap. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:00(2 copies) (Box 33)
  - GINI. Les Coups de Foudre GINI. 1981-1993. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 33)
  - Ginsu Knives. Commercial. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 33)
  - Gold Pages. Stone and Adler radio Spots. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 240:00(2 tapes) (Box 33)
  - Goldeneye
    - Commercials (France). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:20 (Box 33)
    - Commercials (France). 1997. VHS. SECAMTRT: 1:20 (Box 33)
    - Trailer. 1997. Betacam SP. NTSC. TRT: 2:53 (Box 33)
  - Grahams Jewellers. Gold Range; Rings; Watches. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 33)
  - Grolier Enterprises
    - Beginning Readers Program. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 33)
    - Disney Book Club. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 33)
  - Grolier Enterprises (Box 34)
    - Disney Book Club: Disney in a Bag. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 34)
    - Disney Book Club: Disney Santa. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 34)
    - Disney Book Club: Mommy. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 34)
    - Great Indoor website. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 5:00(2 copies) (Box 34)
    - Happy Plants. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
    - New Book of Knowledge. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 17:00 (Box 34)
    - Prevention Health Nut. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 34)
    - Thank You--Cat in the Hat. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
  - GTE. Spot (Puerto Rico). Undated. VHS. TRT: 20:00 (Box 34)
  - Guggenheim. National Heritage campaign. 1997. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
  - Harlequin Books
    - At the Beach; Can Dreams Come True. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:30(2 copies) (Box 34)
    - The Love Affair. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 34)
  - HBO (Box 35)
    - Commercial. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box 35)
    - Commercials. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 2:15 (Box 35)
    - Is Going Out Worth the Trouble? 1995. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 35)
  - HCA (Hospital Corporation of America)
    - Commercials: Whole World of Caring; Quality of Care; Corporate Message; Care Program; Physician Quality; Care Card; Houston Outpatient Surgery. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 35)
    - Health Plans; Health Plans/Start Over. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 35)
  - HDM. Agency Reel: Peugeot; Dannon; Colgate; Mita; Hertz. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 35)
  - Heinz/Idal. Q. B. Tomato Pulp. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:20 (Box 35)
  - Hills Pet Products
    - Hills Big Bang. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
    - Radio spots: Walking the Dog; Pet Store; Grocery Store; Soups On; Play Things; The Vet; The Traveler. 1988. Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box 35)
  - Holiday Inn
    - Hotels. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 35)
    - On the House. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:15 (Box 35)
    - Sweepstakes. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 35)
  - Hudson Vitamins. Spiderman. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 0:55 (Box 35)
  - Hughes Avicom International. Strapping in Worldlink Operating Instructions. 1993. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 35)
  - Huntington's Disease Society of America
    - Nanny's Birthday: You're Not Sick, You've Only Got HD. Undated. VHS. TRT: 38:00 (Box 35)
    - Public Service: Attic. 1992. VHS. TRT: 15:00 (Box 35)
  - I Love Lucy (television program) (Box 36)
    - Lucy's Italian Movie, show no. 150. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 36)
    - Lucy's Troubles Managing Money. Part 1. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 15:00 (Box 36)
    - Million Dollar Idea, show no. 79. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 36)
    - Switching Jobs, show no. 30. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 36)
    - The Freezer, show no. 29. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 36)
  - Icehouse (beer). Watered Down Demo/Mop Up; Iceland. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 36)
  - Ikea
    - Balloon (Singapore). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 36)
    - Christmas promotion (Singapore). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:45(2 copies) (Box 36)
  - Impiric
    - AT&T spots: Bad Commedian; Imagination; DPS. Straw/Free Month; Installation Guy; Teenager; Rhett and Scarlett; Stretch; Playtime; Street Talk; Blind Date. 2001. Umatic. TRT: 8:30 (Box 36)
    - Landor-Journey Logo Reveal. 2000. Betacam SP. TRT: 10:00 (Box 36)
  - Impiric (Box 37)
    - Opener. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 4:51 (Box 37)
    - Post Requests Master. 2000. Betacam SP. TRT: 60:00 (Box 37)
    - Rebranding Master, Tapes 1-9. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 540:00 (Box 37)
    - Rebranding Keepsake. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 37)
    - Rebranding Show, Lester Wunderman Speech. 2000. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 37)
    - Rebranding tapes 4-5. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box 37)
  - INA Duemila. Spot radio 3x30" (Italy). 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box 38)
  - Intel. Pentium II: J. Alexander and Mom. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 38)
  - Interactive Channel
    - Awareness spots. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 38)
    - Lost Birthday. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 9:30 (Box 38)
    - Lost Birthday. 1996. VHS. TRT: 9:30 (Box 38)
    - Source Media. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 38)
    - Source Media. 1996. VHS. TRT: 0:30 (Box 38)
  - International Correspondence School. ICS/CDS. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
  - Italia Petroli
    - National promotion (WCJ Milan). 1994. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 30:00 (Box 38)
    - Win the American Dream. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 38)
  - It's Your Business (television program). Show no. 729, Electronic Monitoring. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 38)
  - ITT. ITT Focus. 1999. VHS. TRT: 3:10 (Box 38)
  - ITT Tech. 3D HSC Show, Sept. 1997. 2000. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 38)
  - Jack Frost. Generic; Queens Festival; 116th St. Festival; Expo Feria. 1990. VHS. TRT: 1:50 (Box 38)
  - J. C. Penney Portrait Studio. New Business Presentation, Portraits. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
  - Johnson & Johnson
    - Band Aid: Stuck on Me Travolta/Garr. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 38)
    - Child Development: Explorer. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 38)
    - Child Development: In the Hands of a Baby. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 38)
    - Child Development: Inside the Box; So Much to Learn. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
  - Johnson & Johnson (Box 39)
    - Child Development: New Babies. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 39)
    - Child Development: Racquetball; Yuppie Picnic; Explorer; Roger; Birthday; Bare Bottom; Discovery; In the Hand of a Baby. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 39)
    - Child Development: Yuppie Picnic; Racquetball. 1985. 1" Video reel. TRT: Undetermined. (2 reels) (Box 39)
    - Stayfree: Children's Miracle. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 0:15 (Box 39)
    - Stayfree Maxi Pads: 100 Year Anniversary. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 0:15 (Box 39)
    - Stayfree Ultra: Mujeres al Borde. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 39)
    - Various: Take a Powder Goose Gossage; Take a Powder Nancy Lieberman; Shower. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 39)
  - Kendall/Curity
    - Curity Incontinent w/Wrap; Turn, Turn, Turn; Participate; All Year Long Neil Sedaka; All Year Long. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 39)
    - Curity Incontinent: You're Not Alone animatic. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 39)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken. A Trollear promotion (WCJ Puerto Rico). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 39)
  - Kessler & Associates (Box 40)
    - Real Life: Free; $5. 00. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 40)
    - Real Life: Obstacles; Information; Success Test; Report; Huggable. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 40)
    - Real Life: Success Test; Report; Information; Obstacles. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 40)
    - Real Life: Obstacles; Update; Qualifier; Hot Button. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 13:00 (Box 40)
  - Keycorp. Skyscraper. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 40)
  - KGF. Reel for KGF Norway Presentation. France: Milka Spa. Argentina: Lila Pause Cricket. U. S.: Budget Gourmet Under $2. 00. Mexico: Sugus Train. Greece: Jacobs Coffee Pop Bowtie. France: Roche Night. Denmark: Toblerone Madame. Sweden: Gevalia Seduction. Chile: Glue Rocking Chair. Tokyo: Scotch Fish. LATAM: Dr. Scholl's Fisherman. Amsterdam: Sony Cranebird. LATAM: Telemundo TV Soccer Players. Zurich: Dairy Dancing Cow. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 40)
  - Kiawah & Carmel. Best of Kiawah & Carmel. 141 items. 1995-1996. Umatic. TRT: 41:17 (Box 40)
  - Kingsford Charcoal
    - Amateur Hour; Hot Line; Stereo. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 40)
    - BBQ Idea Line. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 40)
  - Kraft Foods Corporation. Kraft Real Mayonnaise: Lobster; Broadway/Actress; Alligator; Alligator Blue Pirate; Madame Enduro; Mayor Holden; Little Connie. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 40)
  - Kraft Jacobs Suchard (KJC). Milka: Cow for Every Family (Prague). Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 0:10 (Box 40)
  - Labatt's Beer. Blue Light; Labatt Lite. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 40)
  - Leo Burnett Company. Regional Creative Review CYBDT. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 40)
  - Lester Wunderman
    - American Express Sales Meeting. 1989. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 40)
    - Amsterdam presentation. New York Telephone: Pick Me Up; 10 Minute Talker; George; Umbrella. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 40)
    - Art of the Dogon. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 40)
  - Lester Wunderman (Box 41)
    - Direct Marketing Concepts. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00(5 copies) (Box 41)
    - Direct Marketing Man of the Year. 1982. Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00 (Box 41)
    - Direct Marketing speech. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - DMIX speech. 1980. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:00 (Box 41)
    - Lester Wunderman Presents. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box 41)
    - Presentation at Direct Marketing Workshop. Time Magazine: Wilderness; Time Flies. Time Life Books: Home Repair. Fritz wrap spot for Mercury. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Presentation cassette: Witness Segment. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 41)
    - Presentation tape 1: Charlie Chaplin clip from Modern Times; Woody Allen clips from Sleeper (Robot, Tailor). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 41)
    - Presentation tape 2: Saturday Night Live, Larry the Lobster. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 41)
    - Time Inc. Direct Marketing Day Seminar presentation. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
  - Lester Wunderman Tributes
    - AAF Awards tribute. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 1: Lloyd Morrissett. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 1: Lloyd Morrissett. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 2: Lester Wunderman. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 3: Richard Thoman; Steve Dapper; Angela Kapp. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 4: Aldo Pappone; Michael Schlossberg. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 4: Aldo Pappone; Michael Schlossberg. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 5: Peter Georgescu; Steve Goldstein part 1. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
    - Roll 5: Peter Georgescu; Steve Goldstein part 1. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 41)
  - Lester Wunderman Tributes (Box 42)
    - Roll 6: Steve Goldstein (part 2); Lenny Barshack. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Roll 6: Steve Goldstein (part 2); Lenny Barshack. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Roll 7: George Wiedeman (Grey Direct); Jerry Sheresshewsky (Yahoo). 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Roll 8: Jerry Sheresshewsky (Yahoo. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Roll 9: Ed Ney; Walter Chronkite. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Roll 9: Ed Ney; Walter Chronkite. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Mr. Wunderman, Roll 2. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Mr. Wunderman, Roll 2. 1999. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
  - Levi Strauss. Levi's Wide Leg and Jeans for Women: Elevator Fantasy; Elevator Fantasy Jr.; Doctors; Shake It; Shine. 1997. VHS. TRT: 3:30 (Box 42)
  - Lincoln-Mercury
    - 34 International commercials. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Do You Want to Dance?; Proud Mary. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 42)
    - Ford Exchange: 51 international commercials. 1998. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 42)
    - Grand Marquis. 1998. VHS. TRT: 5:00 (Box 42)
    - Home Sweet Home. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 42)
    - Home Sweet Home. 2000. VHS. TRT: 0:30 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln. Untitled. 1997. VHS. TRT: 5:00 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Continental. 1995. VHS. TRT: 5:00(2 copies) (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Mark VIII1997. VHS. TRT: 20:00 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Mark VIII: Temptation. 1997. VHS. TRT: 5:00 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Navigator: Anywhere James. 1998. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Navigator: Black Lincoln; Home on the Range. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Navigator: Black Lincoln; Home on the Range. 1998. VHS. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 42)
    - Lincoln Town Car. 1998. VHS. TRT: 5:00 (Box 42)
  - Lincoln-Mercury (Box 43)
    - Mercury Sable. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 43)
    - Mercury Sable. 38 spots. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 60:00(2 tapes) (Box 43)
    - Merkur XR4TI Challenge. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 43)
    - Scorpio: Cable direct marketing. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
  - Lorraine Cheese. Deli Cut Superbowl promo. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 43)
  - Lufthansa. Interfly--Internet. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 43)
  - Lycos. Sherpa (Bozell Worldwide). 1998. VHS. TRT: 1:30 (Box 43)
  - M Net. History reel. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 43)
  - Maalox. Maalox PDTS Liquid. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 43)
  - Manspray. Spot (Y&R Denmark). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 43)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust
    - Bankless Banking. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 43)
    - Bankless Banking; Lunch Hour. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 43)
    - Checking N. O. W. /Cirrus. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 43)
    - Corporate Intro; Cirrus. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
    - Credit Wrap. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust (Box 44)
    - Credit Wrap. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
    - Father and Daughter (Mastercard); Waiter (Visa). 1986. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
    - Home Equity Credit Line: Neighbors. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 44)
    - Home Equity Loans: Neighbors. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 44)
    - House. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 44)
    - Image Credit, legal screening. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 44)
    - I. R. A. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:40 (Box 44)
    - Market Plus Accounts/Egg. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
    - Mr. Computer Analyst, radio. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 44)
    - Mr. Conservative Chemist, radio. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 44)
    - Ms. Avon Lady, radio. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 44)
    - One for All Banking Package Account: The Big Idea. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 44)
    - TV wrap: Financial Planning; Domicile Purchase. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 44)
    - Waiter; Domicile. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 44)
    - We Realize Your Potential; Tennis; Soccer; Runner. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 44)
  - Margrace (Box 45)
    - Bullworker: Testimonial. Story of America: That's Incredible. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 9:00 (Box 45)
    - Multi-Reel. 7 spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 14:00 (Box 45)
    - Porta Pedal: Challenger. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 45)
    - Spots: Sportscards, No Strings Attached; Safari Cards, Wild and Wonderful, Elephant. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 10:00(2 copies) (Box 45)
    - War Cards: Pieces Put Together; Family. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 45)
  - McDonald's Corporation
    - Untitled commercial. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 45)
    - Untitled commercial. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 45)
  - Melrose Film Productions. Agreed. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 27:00 (Box 45)
  - Merck. Propecia: Exciting Pill; Angelic Glow. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 45)
  - Merrill Lynch
    - 12 Spots. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 9:30 (Box 45)
    - A New Number Shop/AT&T Break Up; AT&T Stock Fund/Break Up. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 45)
    - Break-Up. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:30(2 copies) (Box 45)
    - Chess. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 45)
  - Merrill Lynch (Box 46)
    - Greenhouse; Haystack. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 46)
    - IRA/Before April 15th. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:50 (Box 46)
    - IRA Sleeping Giant; CD Puzzle Bull w/800#; AT&T Stock Fund Breakup. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 46)
    - Maze; China Shop. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 46)
    - Model. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 46)
    - Model Bull. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 46)
    - Model Revised. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 46)
    - Mt. Climb; Snowfall; Rainstorm; River Cross; Mt. Top BB. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 3:40 (Box 46)
    - Perpetual Motion: Shadow/Bull. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 46)
    - Pockets. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 46)
  - Metropollitan Hodder Group. Press Conference: U. S. Satellite Broadcasting. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 46)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance
    - HIP/HMO. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 46)
    - Melting Pot; Frontier; No Desk Job. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 46)
  - Microsoft. Microsoft Project (Chapman Direct). 1995. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 16:32 (Box 46)
  - Miller Brewing Company
    - Anthem; 1855; You Can Change Too; Dad's Beer; No Map; Innovations; Last Great Places. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 46)
    - Before This; Rod Stewart; Marooned. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 46)
    - Change; No Map; Herd; Innovations; Nature Conservancy. 1991. VHS. TRT: 3:48 (Box 46)
  - Miller Brewing Company (Box 47)
    - Colders 29: Primal/Food/New; Primal/Work/New; Primal/Hunger/New. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 47)
    - Historical reel. 1985-1991. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box 47)
    - International executions 1994. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 47)
    - International executions 1995. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 30:00(2 copies) (Box 47)
    - Miller Genuine Draft: NASCAR Sponsorship on TNN. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 8:20 (Box 47)